# MARY LAURA CARMONA MARTÍNEZ

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT

I am pursuing a career in computer science with a focus on web design and web development. I count with 2+ years of experience in front-end development.

I am an advocate of women in STEM, participating in various projects to promote women taking on science positions.

# CONTACT

- Ŷ
- Puebla, Puebla
- carmonamartinezmarylaura@gmail.com
- **t.**
- +52 (222) 913 9997
- in
- /carmona-martínez-mary-laura

#### **EDUCATION**

## Instituto Tecnológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey • 2022

Bachelor's degree of Engineering in Computer Science and Technology.

#### SKILLS

- Detail-oriented
- · Quick and independent learner
- · Critical thinking
- Adaptability
- Collaboration

# LANGUAGES

Spanish Native

**English** Advanced (C1)

## EXPERIENCE

# FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER. VILLA ATL.

FEB 2022 - JUN 2022.

- UI/UX re-design of the organization's website.
- Design and development of new section for program "Alto Atoyac".
- Tools used: WordPress, HTML, CSS, Adobe XD.

# FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER. PROYECTO25. FEB 2020 - JUN 2020.

- UI/UX design and development of the organization's website.
- Tools used: WordPress, HTML, CSS, Adobe XD.

#### WEB DESIGNER. IMEPLAN PUEBLA.

JAN 2019 - MAY 2019.

- UI/UX re-design of the organization's website.
- UI mock-up creation.
- Tools used: Adobe XD, Photoshop.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML	• • • • •	Ð
CSS	• • • • •	Ð
JavaScript	• • • • •	
React	• • • • •	
Java	• • • • •	
Python	• • • • •	
MySQL	• • • • •	
PostgreSQL	• • • • •	
MongoDB	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$	
PHP	• • • • •	
NodeJS	• • • • •	
GraphQL	• • • • •	
Docker	• • • • •	
Git	• • • • •	